Thakur Chandan Kumar

| +91-8291881211 |

| Plot No-21, Shiv Pooja, Shop No-02, Sector No-01, Sanpada, Navi Mumbai, IN | | CONTACT24.7CKT@GMAIL.COM |

Information Technology Specialist

Develop, Implement, Monitor and Support information systems programs

IT specialist with a passion and talent for aligning architecture, plans, controls, processes, policies and procedures with security standards and operational goals. Project leader with proven experience directing all phases of complex projects while managing, motivating and mentoring global team members. Extensive experience developing and testing security architectures of cloudbased systems.

Technology Skills					
Security:	Vulnerability-scanning, Web gateway, proxy appliances and antivirus tools, Web Scripting, Web Scraping.				
Systems:	Experience working in mixed Windows/Linux, database and virtualized/physical server environments.				
Programming:	Knowledge of C, Java, JavaScript, jQuery, Python, PHP, HTML5, CSS, MySQL.				

Experience

Network Technology, Sanpada, Navi Mumbai | 01/06/2015 to 15/04/2017 Hardware & Networking Engineers and Office Administration.

In this organization, I will be attending customer call for system maintenance and formatting and office administrator.

One Point One Solutions, Turbhe, Navi Mumbai | 01/05/2017 to 30/10/2017 Customer Relations Executive.

In this organization, I will be attending customer call for order processing and solve customer problems.

Network Technology, Sanpada, Navi Mumbai | 01/06/2018 to 28/02/2019 Sr. Hardware & Networking Engineers and Office Administration.

In this organization, I will be attending customer call for system maintenance and formatting and office administrator.

Start-Up Experience, Sanpada, Navi Mumbai | 01/01/2019 to Present. Administrator & Project Leader.

In this, I will be started own organization for Data Entry processing US medical data. And handle all the office Activities and Managing the Project.

Extra Activities

- Ethical Hacking Seminar & Webinar Attended.
- CISCO Webinar Attended.
- * AWS Summit Attended in Mumbai.

Education

Mumbai University, Mumbai, IN Bachelor of Science, Information Technology (2016-2019)

Sem I	Sem II	Sem II	Sem IV	Sem V	Sem VI	Total CGPA & %
7.00	7.40	8.40	9.10	8.70	8.30	8.15 (68.8%)

12 th Maharashtra Board (Maharashtra)	10 th Bihar Board (Bihar)		
56.00 % (With Electronics)	52.20 %		

Personal Details

Nationality Indian

Date of birth 10th March 1998

Gender Male

Marital status Married

Religion Hindu